[
    {
    "option1": "You have be going.",
    "option2": "You have been going.",
    "option3": "You have  gone.",
    "option4": "You are going.",
    "question": "তুমি যেতে থাকছো",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You will be going.",
    "option2": "You will be gone.",
    "option3": "You shall be going.",
    "option4": "You are going.",
    "question": "তুমি যেতে থাকবে",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You had been gone.",
    "option2": "You were going.",
    "option3": "You had going.",
    "option4": "You had been going.",
    "question": "তুমি যেতে থেকেছিলে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Are you been going ?",
    "option2": "Have you been gone ?",
    "option3": "Have you been going ?",
    "option4": "Had you been going ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি যেতে থাকছো ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will you been going ?",
    "option2": "Will you be going ?",
    "option3": "Shall you be going ?",
    "option4": "Are you be going ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি যেতে  থাকবে ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had you been going ?",
    "option2": "Had you going ?",
    "option3": "Have you been going ?",
    "option4": "Had you be going ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি যেতে  থাকছিলে ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
     {
    "option1": "You have gone.",
    "option2": "You had went.",
    "option3": "You had gone.",
    "option4": "You had been gone.",
    "question": "তুমি গেলে",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had you gone ?",
    "option2": "Had you go ?",
    "option3": "Was you gone ?",
    "option4": "Had you went ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি গেলে ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You could had gone.",
    "option2": "You could have gone.",
    "option3": "You can have gone.",
    "option4": "You could go.",
    "question": "তুমি যেতে পারতে",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Could you had gone ?",
    "option2": "Could you have go ?",
    "option3": "Could you have gone ?",
    "option4": "Could you had went ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি যেতে পারতে ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You would had gone.",
    "option2": "You was have gone.",
    "option3": "You would have go.",
    "option4": "You would have gone.",
    "question": "তুমি যেতে পারতে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Would you had gone ?",
    "option2": "Would you have gone ?",
    "option3": "Would you have been gone ?",
    "option4": "Would you have go ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি যেতে পারতে ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
     {
    "option1": "You should have gone.",
    "option2": "You should had gone.",
    "option3": "You could have gone.",
    "option4": "You should have went.",
    "question": "তোমার যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Should you had gone ?",
    "option2": "Would you have gone ?",
    "option3": "Should you have going ?",
    "option4": "Should you have gone ?",
    "question": "তোমার কি যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You may have went.",
    "option2": "You may have gone.",
    "option3": "You may be have gone.",
    "option4": "You may have going.",
    "question": "তুমি যেতে পারতে",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "May you have gone ?",
    "option2": "May you had gone ?",
    "option3": "May you has gone ?",
    "option4": "May you have go ?",
    "question": "তুমি কি যেতে পারতে ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You can but not go.",
    "option2": "You cannot but going.",
    "option3": "You cannot but go.",
    "option4": "You cannot but went.",
    "question": "তুমি না গিয়ে পারো না",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "You can help  not going.",
    "option2": "You cannot help going.",
    "option3": "You cannot helped going.",
    "option4": "You cannot help go.",
    "question": "তুমি না গিয়ে পারো না",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]